Jubair

Aroor, Alappuzha, Kerala

८ +91-9544403799 **☑** jubaircj02042001@gmail.com **in** Jubair c j **⊙** jubaircj

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a diligent software developer who is passionate about web development and machine learning. I have acquired strong skills in the web development domain with numerous projects and an internship. I am a curious learner and would like to put into practice my knowledge and experience and in turn help the organisation achieve its goals.

EDUCATION

College of Engineering Trivandrum

BTech Computer Science

 $Aug\ 2019-July\ 2023$

Trivandrum, Kerala

Vaduthala Jama-ath Higher Secondary School

Computer Science - Percentage - 85%

May 2017 – March 2019

EXPERIENCE

Kompetenzen Technologies, Kochi - internship

Oct 2023 - present

Alappuzha, Kerala

• Internship on full stack development using Java(Core Java + JSP Servlets + Hibernate + Spring + SpringBoot).

Chegg - Freelance Worker

Jan 2021 - June 2023

• Worked as a Computer Science Expert in Chegg as a freelance worker.

CERTIFICATIONS

• 5 days Internship on Open Street Mapping conducted by NSS CET

PROJECTS

Development of a Smart Network Intrusion Detection System

• Designed and implemented a highly accurate AI-based real-time network intrusion detection and prevention system achieving 96computational efficiency and utilizing real-time analysis for predictive system implementation.

Made a clone of OLX and NETFLIX

• Developed using React JS

Personal Website

• A static website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JQuery.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Java, Python, C, C++, JavaScript
- Web Technologies: HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, React JS(Beginner)
- Others: SQL, Git, Latex, Basics of Machine Learning

ACTIVITIES

Google Cloud Sep 2021

Architecting with Google Compute Engine Specialization

Management May 2022

Drishti(Technical fest of CET)

Rajvapuraskar Holder

2013-2019

Member in Bharat Scouts and Guides